Inventory of the Media Collection, 1928 - [ongoing]
Media Collection, 1928 - [ongoing]
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-78
12
23
Wesleyan-related audio and video recordings in multiple formats.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Consult with Special Collections & Archives staff for availability of listening copies.
Acquisitions Information
Gradual accretion of transfers and gifts.
Collection Overview
The Wesleyan University Media Collection is arranged in series by media type. Material within each series is arranged in numerical order. Each series starts with Box 1 and item one, so that new material can easily be added without shifting boxes or changing box numbers. An earlier system, for example, did not always distinguish between a reel-to-reel audio tape and an audio cassette. Both would be given the next number and then housed in the same box. Housing material in different formats in the same container has been discontinued.
Eight series have been established. Series I: Tape Recordings consists of reel-to-reel audiotapes. The tapes carry the prefix TW followed by an item number. Items that are on audiocassettes are found in Series III. Series II: Video Recordings consists primarily of films on videocassette. These items carry the prefix VTW followed by an item number. The videocassettes are primarily in VHS format, although a few are Betamax and are noted in the listing. Series III: Audiocassettes consists of material on audiocassette and carry the prefix AC followed by a number. Since some cassettes had been accessioned as a TW number, cross references have been placed from TW to AC. Example: Wesleyan Spirits in Concert at Alpha Delta Phi (TW 86) see: Audio Cassette AC 5. Series IV: CD format. Series V: Oversize items, followed by a number. There are cross-references from the original series to the oversize location. Series VI: Unprocessed Material consists of music disks and reel-to-reel films in metal canisters. Some general description of this material is available in the collections file for this series. Series VII: DVD format. Series VIII: Record albums.
Some items are available in more than one format. When this occurs, a cross reference is made. For example, the Jeffrey Schiff videotape of the Library Project Symposium is also available as a DVD, so a cross reference is made from VTW 38 to CD/DVD 1. It should be noted that there is one tape (TW 32) that is labeled as confidential.
Collection Arrangement
Series I: Tape Recordings
Series II: Video Recordings
Series III: Audio Cassettes
Series IV: CD Recordings
Series V: Oversize
Series VI: Unprocessed Material
Series VII: DVDs
Series VIII: Record Albums
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Audiocassettes.; Compact Discs.; DVDs.; Video recordings.; Phonograph records.; Audiotapes.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.
Related Material
Archives Vertical Files photograh collection
Wesleyan University Photographs Collection, Collection 1000-108
Additional Wesleyan music and dance recordings are available in the Scores and Recordings Library and the Wesleyan Library’s circulating media collections.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Tape recordings
  - Commencement, 1957: Scots Guards (bagpipes), TW 1: (Box 1)
  - Commencement, 1958: Alumni Sing, TW 2:
    See also CD 18.
  - Commencement, June 7, 1959, TW 3:
    See also CD 23a and CD 23b.
  - Commencement, June 12, 1960, TW 4:
  - Commencement, 1960: Alumni Luncheon, June 11, 1960, TW 5:
  - Commencement, 1961: Alumni Luncheon, June 13, 1961, TW 6:
  - Commencement, June 7, 1964, TW 7:
    See also audio cassette AC 1.
  - Commencement, June 5, 1966, TW 8:
  - Commencement 1963: Alumni Seminars, May 31, 1963, TW 9: (Box 2)
    Nelson W. Polsby, E.Q. Daddario '39, Joseph Tussman, A.E. Sutherland '23.
  - Commencement 1966: Alumni Seminars, June 2, 1966, TW 10:
    R.C. Flewelling '16, B.A. Passett '56, F.O. Glover, Jr. '66: Changing Concepts in City Planning
  - Commencement 1967: Alumni Seminar I, TW 11:
    John W. Macy '38, Fred B. Millett.
  - Commencement 1967: Alumni Seminar II, TW 12:
    Carl E. Schorske.
  - Commencement 1967: Alumni Seminar III, TW 13:
    Rene Dubos, W. Waldo Beach '37, R.F. Haglund, Jr. '67, D. A. Egar '67.
  - Matriculation Service, September 21, 1960: V.L. Butterfield., TW 14:
  - Matriculation Service, September 20, 1961: V.L. Butterfield., TW 15:
  - Matriculation Service, September 20, 1962: V.L. Butterfield., TW 16:
  - Matriculation Service, September 23, 1963: V.L. Butterfield., TW 17:
  - Matriculation Service, September 22, 1965: V.L. Butterfield., TW 18: (Box 3)
  - Convocation in Honor of Scholarship, Oct. 9, 1965: Edward Williamson.
  - Freshman Symposium September 11, 1960: V.L. Butterfield, R.K. Winslow., TW 19:
  - Freshman Orientation, 1961., TW 20:
  - The College in Transition, Eugene O. Golob, Norman O. Brown, Sept. 14, 1960., TW 21:
    See also CD 24a and CD 24b.
  - The College in Transition, D.P. McAllester, W.M. Wallace, R.K. Winslow, Sept. 14, 1960., TW 22:
    See also CD 21a and CD 21b.
  - The College in Transition, L.O. Mink, Jr., R.A. Rosenbaum, V.W. Cochrane, Sept. 14, 1960., TW 23:
    See also CD 20a and CD 20b.
  - Convocation in Honor of Scholarship: Prof. Reginald F. Arragon, Reed College, October 26, 1960, TW 24:
  - Symposium: The Spanish Civil War in Historical Perspective, Hon. John D. Lodge, Allen Gutman (Amherst), William Watson (M.I.T.), Juan Marichal (Harvard), undated., TW 25:
  - Career Conference on Journalism: Bayard Webster, William Manchester, John W. Kiermaier '43, Robert Eddy, Alphonsus J. Mitchell, May 4, 1966, TW 26: (Box 4)
  - Psi Upsilon Conference, April 1958: T.G. Henney, D.E. Swift, Paul R. Levine '58:Does Wesleyan Fulfill the Needs of Its Students?, TW 27:
  - Davison Dinner, New York City, 1959, TW 28:
  - V.L. Butterfield: The College Plan, Feb. 11, 1959, TW 29:
  - V.L. Butterfield, Julian D. Anthony '28: 125th Anniversary of Phi Nu Theta (Eclectic), Oct. 27, 1962, TW 30:
    See also CD 22.
  - V.L. Butterfield on Channel 30: Five College Presidents: An Exchange of Views, Feb. 3, 1965, TW 31:
  - V.L. Butterfield at Faculty Meeting, Dec 13, 1955?, TW 32:
    See also CD 25.
  - E.D. Etherington at annual dinner of Middletown Chamber of Commerce: Wesleyan and Middletown – In Tandem for Tomorrow, June 13, 1966, TW 33:
  - E.D. Etherington: Inaugural Address, Oct. 21, 1967, TW 34:
  - Hannah Arendt in Memorial Chapel, Nov. 20, 1965, TW 35: (Box 5)
  - Ralph Bunche., TW 36:
  - Walter G. Cady in Russel House garden, May 19, 1964: Recollections of Physics at Wesleyan, TW 37:
    Transcription available in University Archives at call number Wes F C12.
  - Douglass Cater, Honors College, April 21, 1960: Politics and the Reporter, TW 38:
  - Douglass Cater, Memorial Chapel, Dec. 6, 1961: Kennedy Administration-First Year Appraisal., TW 39:
  - Gilbert H. Clee '35, Faculty Club Luncheon, Oct. 7, 1960, TW 40:
    See also CD 19.
  - Robert Frost, Memorial Chapel: Assembly Series and Poetry Festival, May 19, 1960, TW 41:
  - Wilbert Snow: My Friend, Robert Frost, TW 42:
  - Alger Hiss, Memorial Chapel, Oct. 7, 1965: The U.N.-Promise and Performance., TW 43: (Box 6)
  - Paul Horgan, Sir Herbert Read, John W. Paton '49, Feb. 28, 1964 On the Center for Advanced Studies., TW 44:
  - John D. Maguire and David E. Swift, Memorial Chapel, May 26, 1961:Freedom Rides., TW 45:
    See also: Audio Cassette AC 2.
  - William Manchester: Americana Interview, April 4, 1966, TW 46:
  - Lewis Mumford, John Wesley Club Forum, Nov. 7, 1963: The Human Prospect., TW 47:
  - Lewis Mumford, Memorial Chapel, Nov. 14, 1963: Dehumanized Men and Humanized Machines., TW 48:
  - Abraham Ribicoff, Governor, Memorial Chapel, Oct. 28, 1959: The Relation of Political Theory to Reality., TW 49:
  - Freshman Orientation: Elmer E.Schattschneider, Sept. 12, 1961 Traditions., TW 50:
  - Sir Charles P. Snow, Recent Thoughts on the Two Cultures, December 1961, TW 51: (Box 51)
  - Norman Thomas, Memorial Chapel, Oct. 25, 1965, United States Foreign Policy: Viet Nam, TW 52:
  - Paul J. Tillich, hon. ’57: Matchette Lecture I, April 10, 1958, The Meaning of Religion and the Protestant Principle., TW 53:
  - Paul J. Tillich, hon. ’57: Matchette Lecture II, April 11, 1958, The Inner Dynamics of Contemporary Religions., TW 54:
  - Tilich Lectures I and II on one reel, TW 54a:
  - Paul J. Tillich, hon. ’57: Matchette Lecture III, April 12, 1958, Religion’s Convergencies and Divergences and the Protestant Principle., TW 55:
  - Tilich Lectures III, copy 2, TW 55a:
  - Bishop Herbert Welch ’87 on His 100th Birthday, Nov. 7, 1962., TW 56:
  - Henry M. Wriston ’11, New York City, April 19, 1966:, TW 57:
    Conversation with Alphonsus J. Mitchell. Transcription available at Special Collections & Archives at call number Wes/1911/W95.
  - Commencement: V.L. Butterfield, June 4, 1967., TW 58:
  - Baccalaureate Service: Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr., Denison Terrace, June 7, 1964, TW 59: (Box 8)
    Heavily abridged transcript appears in the Wesleyan University Alumnus, May 1968. See also: Audio Cassettes AC 3a-b.
  - Re-recording of the MLK Baccalaureate Service, March 1981, TW 59a:
    See also: Audio Cassettes AC 3a-b.
  - Prof. Daniel Mazia and Prof. Albert L. Lehninger, ’39: Addresses at dedication of Hall-Atwater laboratories, Oct. 11, 1968., TW 60:
  - Prof. Frank W. Putnam ’39 and Prof. George Wald: Addresses at symposium and dedication of Hall-Atwater Laboratories, Oct. 11, 1968, TW 61:
  - Prof. George Hammond: Address at symposium and dedication of Hall-Atwater laboratories, Oct. 12, 1968, TW 62:
  - Ceremonies at dedication of Hall-Atwater Laboratories: remarks by Prof. R.A. Gortner, Jr., and Vice-President Robert A. Rosenbaum, Oct. 12, 1968., TW 63:
  - MISSING: Commencement Address: Julian Bond, June 8, 1969, TW 64:
  - MISSING: Andrew J. Young, D.D.: Address at Senior Class Memorial Convocation, McConaughy Hall, June 8, 1969, TW 65:
  - Colin G. Campbell: Address to the Wesleyan Community, McConaughy Hall, Feb. 8, 1972., TW 66:
    Printed in the Wesleyan Argus, Feb. 9 and 11, 1972
  - Burton H. Camp, ’01: Conversation with Alphonsus J. Mitchell about Wesleyan experiences, Nov. 1971, TW 67:
  - Burton H. Camp, ’01: Further conversation with Alphonsus J. Mitchell about Wesleyan experiences, May 12, 1972, TW 68: (Box 9)
  - 140th Commencement, May 24, 1972: C.G. Campbell, Pres.; Carl E. Schorske, speaker., TW 69:
  - Alumni Luncheon: Philip Brown ’44, Colin G. Campbell, et. al., May 27, 1972, TW 70:
  - MISSING: James Farmer, Feb. 1968, TW 71:
  - MISSING: James Farmer, Memorial Chapel, May 10, 1968, TW 72:
  - MISSING: Day of Concern: Panel Discussion, April 25, 1968, TW 73a-e:
    5 reels.
  - MISSING: Ujamaa Statement, Dec. 16, 1969, TW 74:
  - Colin G. Campbell Inauguration, Sept. 18, 1971., TW 75:
  - MISSING: Rev. Burry, E.D. Etherington, S. Newcombs, G. Lang, V. McGuire, Middletown Clergy; Chapel: After Martin Luther King, Jr.’s death, April 5, 1968, TW 76:
  - MISSING: Rev. Burry, E.D. Etherington, S. Newcombs, G. Lang, V. McGuire, Middletown Clergy; Chapel: After Martin Luther King, Jr.’s death, April 5, 1968, TW 76:
  - MISSING: Rev. Burry, E.D. Etherington, S. Newcombs, G. Lang, V. McGuire, Middletown Clergy; Chapel: After Martin Luther King, Jr.’s death, April 5, 1968, TW 76:
  - President Etherington Resignation, Feb. 7, 1969, TW 77:
    See: Oversize 1.
  - Etherington Office Vigil, May 5, 1969, TW 78:
    See: Oversize 2.
  - Fisk Hall Siege, 1968, TW 79:
    2 reels. Stored in Oversize as OS 6.
  - Open Line – Coeducation at Wesleyan, Dec. 12, 1971, TW 80:
    See: Oversize 3.
  - Commencement 1970, TW 81:
  - Harrison Sayre ’17 interviewed by Cliff Saxon of Public Information Office, March 6, 1974, TW 82-83:
    2 reels.
  - WESU midnight news and Butterfield comment by Marjorie Daltry, day of VLB’s death, Nov. 19, 1975, TW 84:
    2 copies. See also CD 34.
  - [1982 Development Campaign Kickoff Dinner, Colin Campbell address (master tape)], October 23, 1982, TW 85: (Box 10)
    Missing. See Audio Cassette AC 4.
  - Wesleyan Spirits, in concert at Alpha Delta Phi, April 26, 1982, TW 86:
    See Audio Cassette AC 5.
  - Charles Olson, Memorial Program, November 18, 1970, TW 87:
  - Carl Schorske, Kokoschka and the birth of Expressionist Culture. April 15, 1964, TW 88:
  - Sir Herbert Read, Kokoschka, Visionary and Symbolic Humanist. 1964, TW 89:
  - Sir Herbert Read, lecture on Pop Art, 1964, TW 90:
  - Benjamin Rowland, lecture, 1967, TW 91:
  - Agnes Mongan, lecture, April 5, 1967, TW 92:
  - President Butterfield: Last Commencement Address, 1967, TW 93:
  - National Student Strike: The Three Demands and Wesleyan University, May 10, 1970, TW 94:
    See also: Audio Cassette AC 6. See also: Oversize 4.
  - Friends of Wesleyan Library talk by Fred A. Pottle: Boswell’s Daughter Euphemia. June 12, 1979, TW 95:
  - Friends of Wesleyan Library: panel discussion on the use of rare books in undergraduate instruction. John Lancaster, George Miles, Ruth Mortimer. April 8, 1985, TW 96: (Box 11)
    See: Audio Cassette AC 7.
  - Wesleyan Sings, historic tape compiled by Betsy Potts: Glee Club, Jibers, and Cardinals, TW 97:
    See: Audio Cassette AC 8.
  - Wesleyan Spirits: The Spirits, tenth anniversary album, recordings from 1981-1991., TW 98:
    See: Audio Cassette AC 9.
  - Wesleyan’s Winslow, Glee Club 1959-1967, compiled by Betsy Potts., TW 99:
    See: Audio Cassette AC 10.
  - Fiftieth Reunion, Class of 1918. June 8-9, 1968, TW 100:
  - 55th Reunion, Class of 1918. June 9, 1973, TW 101:
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Food & Spirits., TW 102:
    See: CD 2.
  - Wesleyan Challenge, Eli Segal, April 9, 1994, TW 103:
    See also: Audio Cassette 11.
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Thundercats, 2000, TW 104:
    See: CD 3.
  - From the Vault: Sampler from Wesleyan World Music Archives, 1996, TW 105a:
    See also: Audio Cassette AC 12.
  - From the Vault: Sampler from Wesleyan World Music Archives, 1996, TW 105b:
    See: CD 4.
  - BOCA: Best of College Acappella, Wesleyan Spirits, TW 106:
    See: CD 5.
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Espiritus, TW 107:
    See: CD 6.
  - The New Group, Newology, TW 108:
    See: CD 7.
  - Abner Mikua: Hugo L. Black lecture, February 19, 1996, TW 109:
    See: Audio Cassette AC 13.
  - Wesleyan Songs Sung by the 1937 Glee Club., TW 110:
    See: CD 8. (Master of 78rpm version in archives)
  - Ken Kwiatkowski ’95, original songs, TW 111:
    See: AC 14.
  - Alumni Luncheon Remarks, 1951-1954: Pres. Butterfield, C.B. Stone, J.E. Stiles, Perigrue., TW 112-TW 117:
  - Wesleyan Glee Club, 1950-1951, TW 118:
    See: CD 9.
  - Jon Silkin reading his poems, Davison Room, Olin Library, Mar 24, 1967, TW 119: (Box 12)
  - Donald Justice reading his poems, Davison Room, Olin Library, April 13, 1967, TW 120:
  - Lou Lipsitz reading his poems, Davison Room, Olin Library, April 13, 1967, TW 121:
  - Richard Howard, Donald Peterson poetry readings, Nov. 11, 1967, TW 122:
  - Honors College poetry readings; Philip Levine and Marge Piercy, March 7, 1968, TW 123:
  - Tony Connor Honors College poetry reading, Sept. 26, 1968, TW 124a-b:
    2 tapes.
  - 1963 Summer School (very light) concert, TW 125a-c:
    3 tapes. See also AC20a-b and CD17a-b.
- Series II: Video Recordings
  Items in this series are in VHS format unless otherwise noted.
  - Wesleyan 157th Commencement Ceremony, May 28, 1989, VTW 1: (Box 1)
  - Wesleyan 158th Commencement Ceremony, June 3, 1990, VTW 2:
  - Wesleyan 159th Commencement Ceremony, June 2, 1990, VTW 3:
  - Wesleyan 160th Commencement Ceremony, May 31, 1992, VTW 4:
  - Dewitt Baldwin ’19 eyewitness account of the San Francisco Earthquake of April 18, 1906: Channel 7 with Paul Berry In Person., VTW 5-6:
    Parts 1 and 2.
  - Wesleyan Reunion: Wesleyan/Bowdoin football game, 1928, VTW 7:
    Footage by Ernest Leighton ’09, gift of Alan Leighton.
  - Wesleyan 167th Commencement, May 30, 1999, VTW 8:
  - Remember This, with Al Roker, 1996, VTW 9a-c:
    3 tapes of Wesleyan team on nationally-televised NBC quiz show.
  - Wesleyan 164th Commencement, 1996, VTW 10:
  - Upward Bound ConnCAP 30th Anniversary, 1996-1997, VTW 11:
  - 164th Commencement, 1996, VTW 12: (Box 2)
    Higginbotham and Senior Class President (Bellavia) Speeches.
  - Cinema Archives 10th Anniversary, 1995, VTW 13: (Box 2)
    Two tapes.
  - Inauguration of Edwin Etherington ’48 as Wesleyan’s President, Oct. 21, 1967, VTW 14:
    VHS copy made from Etherington’s master.
  - Welcome Back to Wesleyan, Reunion Weekend, 1995, VTW 15:
    Highlights tape.
  - Wesleyan Freeman Asian Scholars Program, 1995, VTW 16:
    Announcement Tape (2 copies).
  - A Lifetime of Learning, Wesleyan Alumni Reunion, 1994, VTW 17:
  - Welcoming Douglas J. Bennet, Jr. ’59, Fifteenth President of Wesleyan University, April 7, 1995 (2 copies)., VTW 18:
    (2 copies)
  - Inauguration of Douglas Bennet, Oct. 14, 1995, VTW 19a-d:
    Tapes 19a-c are VHS; 19d is Betamax.
  - Inauguration of Douglas Bennet, Oct. 14, 1995, VTW 19e-l: (Box 3)
    Tapes 19e-l are Betamax.
    See also: Audio Cassette AC 16.
  - Wesleyan in the 1930’s, Eight Alumni Reminisce About Life at Wesleyan, Moderated by David Potts ’60, 1999, VTW 20:
    2 copies.
  - 168th Commencement, May 28, 2000, VTW 21:
  - Connecticut Journal PBS, When Martin Luther King Came to Connecticut, Jan. 12, 2001, VTW 22a:
  - Martin Luther King at Wesleyan University, Jan. 12, 2001, VTW 22b:
  - 169th Commencement, May 27, 2001, VTW 23:
  - Baccaleureate Service at Memorial Chapel, May 27, 2001, VTW 24:
  - Kenneth Strzpek, University of Colorado, Schumann Lecture In Environmental Studies, Feb. 5, 2001, VTW 25:
  - Wesleyan in the Early 1960’s: Ideas, Resources, and Action. Rob Rosenbaum, Herb Arnold, John G. Summer ’63, Kirtland Mead ’65, and David Potts, May 2001, VTW 26:
  - Convergence and Other Rituals on the New Haven Green. A Documentary by Elena Oxman and Elihu Rubin featuring Neely Bruce’s composition/performance, 2000-2001, VTW 27:
  - Ned Jackson ’75 reading from The Life of Saint Martin of New York and One Monkey Story, College of Letters, April 3, 2002, VTW 28:
  - Homefront: Connecticut During WWII, CPTV documentary by Rich Hanley, ’93 MALS, 2001, VTW 29: (Box 4)
    Features Wesleyan images.
  - Dr. Jaques Diouf, “Globalization and the Challenge of Food Security,” Raymond E. Baldwin Lecture, Oct. 30, 2000, VTW 30:
  - John T. Noonan, 10th Hugo L. Black Lecture, March 27, 2001, VTW 31:
  - Nat Hentoff, 11th Hugo L. Black Lecture, March 26, 2002, VTW 32:
  - Daniel Schorr, After September 11th, Sept. 25, 2001, VTW 33:
  - Baccalaureate Service, May 26, 2002, VTW 34:
  - 170th Commencement, May 26, 2002, VTW 35:
  - William Julius Wilson, Lemert Memorial Lecture, Oct. 14, 2003, VTW 36: (Box 5)
  - Open forum with William Julius Wilson on Social Theory and the Concept of the Underclass, October 14, 2003, VTW 37:
  - Library Project Symposium, Jeffrey Schiff, November 2003, VTW 38:
    See also: DVD 1.
  - Jeffrey Makala’s Interview on NBC News Channel 30, Connecticut, on Woodrow Wilson at Wesleyan and Middletown, Jan. 7, 2004, VTW 39:
  - Jeffrey Makala’s Interview on NBC News Channel 30, Connecticut, on Woodrow Wilson at Wesleyan and Middletown, Jan. 7, 2004, VTW 39:
  - Living Together, WESeminar 2003, Homecoming/Family Weekend 2003 (Jeremy Zwelling, Rabbi Jonathan Magonet, and Abu-Raki, Oct. 31, 2003, VTW 40:
  - Ethical Choices in an Interconnected World: Keynote address by Peter Singer, DeCamp Professor of Bioethics in the University Center for Human Values at Princeton University, Nov. 13, 2003, VTW 41:
  - Book Arts Symposium, Connecticut College, 2002, VTW 42:
  - Glimpses of Surgical history, 1809-1981, Feb. 26, 1996, VTW 43:
    Narrated by Dr. Charles Perrill ’34.
  - Having Our Say, WESeminar 18, Homecoming, November 1, 2003, VTW 44:
  - 11th Annual Dwight L. Greene Symposium: Change and Challenges: Black Professionals in Television, Nov. 1, 2003, VTW 45a-b:
  - Welcome Back to Wesleyan, Reunion Weekend, 1995, VTW 46:
    1995 highlights tape, 3/4 inch reel-to-reel videotape master. See: OS 4.
    For VHS use copy, see: VTW 15.
  - Russell House: Amitav Ghosh, September 11, 2002, VTW 47:
  - History/Science Lecture: Lewis Pyenson, September 18, 2003, VTW 48:
  - Annual Hugo L. Black Lecture: Rodney A. Smolla, April 12, 2005, VTW 49:
  - Dr. Paul Farmer, Pathologies of Power: Health and Human Rights in the 21st Century, April 6, 2005, VTW 50:
  - 171st Commencement, 2003, VTW 51:
  - The Baldwin Lecture. Speaker: Ted Shaw '76, NAACP, September 20, 2003, VTW 52:
  - The Grateful Dead, Live at Wesleyan, May 3, 1970, VTW 53:
    See also DVD 8 for viewing copy.
    - Scotch 1 inch video tape on reel [master], VTW 53a/OS 7a:
    - Sony Betacam SP, VTW 53b-c/OS 7b-c:
    - VHS, VTW 53d:
  - Alpha Delta Phi Celebrates Cultural History, May 22, 2004, VTW 54:
- Series III: Audio Cassettes
  - Commencement, June 7, 1964, AC 1 (Box 1)
  - John D. Maguire and David E. Swift, Memorial Chapel: Freedom Rides, May 26, 1961, AC 2
    Copy of original, made May 1987.
  - Re-recording of the Martin Luther King Baccalaureate Service, June 7, 1964, AC 3a
    Made March 1981.
  - Listening copy of AC 3a., AC 3b
  - 1982 Development Campaign Kickoff Dinner, Colin Campbell address, Oct. 23, 1982, AC 4
  - Wesleyan Spirits in Concert at Alpha Delta Phi, April 26, 1982, AC 5
  - National Student Strike: The Three Demands and Wesleyan University, May 10, 1970, AC 6
  - Friends of the Wesleyan Library: Panel Discussion on the Use of Rare Books in Undergraduate Instruction. Speakers: John Lancaster, George Miles, Ruth Mortimer, April 8, 1985, AC 7
  - Wesleyan Sings, 1928-62: Glee Club, Jibers, and Cardinals., AC 8
    Historic tape compiled by Betsy Potts.
  - Wesleyan Spirits: “The Spirits”, Tenth Anniversary Album, recordings from 1981-91, 1991, AC 9
  - Wesleyan’s Winslow, Glee Club 1959-1967., AC 10
    Compiled by Betsy Potts.
  - Wesleyan’s Challenge, Eli Segal, April 9, 1994, AC 11
  - From the Vault: A Sampler from Wesleyan University World Music Archives, 1996, AC 12
  - Abner Mikua: Hugo L. Black Lecture, Feb. 19, 1996, AC 13
  - Ken Kwiatkowski ’95, original songs., AC 14
  - Womyn at Play: Songs to Swim by, The Women’s Singer-Songwriter Collective, AC 15 (Box 2)
  - Douglas Bennet Inauguration Eve Dinner, Oct. 14, 1995, AC 16
  - Herb Owen ’37 Whistles for President and Mrs. Bennet, Ocean Reef Club, Key Largo, FL, Jan. 28, 1998, AC 17
  - The Wesleyan Jibers in College Songs and Barber Shop (1943 recording), 1993, AC 18
  - The Priscilla Gale vocal recordings, 1983-2000?, AC 19
  - 1963 Summer School (very light) concert, AC 20a-b
    2 DAT95 cassettes. See also TW 125a-c and CD 17a-b.
- Series IV: CD
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Food and Spirits, CD 2 (Box 1)
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Thundercats, 2000, CD 3
  - From the Vault: A Sampler from the Wesleyan University World Music Archives, 1996, CD 4
  - BOCA: Best of College A Cappella, featuring the Wesleyan University Spirits, CD 5
  - Wesleyan Spirits, Espiritus, CD 6
  - The New Group, Newology, CD 7
  - Wesleyan University Songs Sung by the 1937 Glee Club, CD 8
  - Wesleyan University Glee Club, 1950-1951, CD 9
  - The New Group, Reflective Surface Syndrome, CD 10
  - Wesleyan University: The Bennet Years, 2007, CD 11
  - Wesleyan University, Commencement 1960, CD 12
  - The Asian Asian-American Show, presented by the Mabuhay Planning Committee, 2008, CD 13
    Playlist: 1) Fan Dance; 2) Filipino Dance; 3) Kaba Wockeez; 4) Jabba Modern; 5) Walk it Out; 6) Thai Fingernail Dance; 7) Soap Opera Opening; 8) Soap Opera Fight; 9) Soap Opera Death and Closing; 10) Fusion Hip Hop; 11) Bollywood; 12) Walk it Out